(Howard:)Never mind.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Hello, Amy. It's Sheldon.
Yeah, I-I know
that we're broken up, but
(Sheldon(on phone):)I'm leaving this message because
I thought perhaps you'd like
(Sheldon(on phone):)to watch me be interviewed for
a documentary about Mr. Spock.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Or as I like to call it,
a Spockumentary.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Yeah, I'm going to use
(Sheldon(on phone):)that joke in the interview,
so try to laugh
(Sheldon(on phone):)like you're hearing it
for the first time.
(Sheldon(on phone):)You know, hysterically, hmm?
(Sheldon(on phone):)And with a tinge of sadness
that I'm no longer in your life.
(Leonard:)I'm the one who thought
of “Spockumentary”"
(Penny:)And I'm laughing like I did
the first time I heard it.
(knocking on door)
(Sheldon(on phone):)Hello.
(Wil Wheaton:)Hey, Sheldon.
(Wil Wheaton:)This is Adam Nimoy.
(Adam:)Nice to meet you.
Oh, it's nice to meet you.
(Sheldon:)I admire your father's work
very much.
(Sheldon:)It's not every day I get to meet
someone whose life's journey
(Sheldon:)began in my hero's scrotum.
(Wil:)I told you.
This guy is gold.